[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the numbers on a dartboard that flank 17?", "correct_answer": "2 and 3", "incorrect_answers": ["16 and 11", "0 and 7", "18 and 13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet of the Solar System is nicknamed the Blue Planet?", "correct_answer": "Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Venus", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the movie which featured the following tag line: Girls like me dont make invitations like this to just anyone!", "correct_answer": "Pulp Fiction", "incorrect_answers": ["Kill Bill Vol. 1", "Kill Bill Vol. 2", "Jackie Brown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the featured family in the film My Big Fat Greek Wedding?", "correct_answer": "Portokalos", "incorrect_answers": ["Melcuri", "Zorba", "Vaidalos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He is considered the first architect whose fame was built on his mall designs.", "correct_answer": "Victor Gruen", "incorrect_answers": ["Hiram Martyn", "Robert G. Perez", "James L. Perez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rodent, closely related to the chinchilla and guinea pig, is also known as the Brush-Tailed Rat and is native to Chile?", "correct_answer": "Degu", "incorrect_answers": ["Gerbil", "White-tailed Antelope Squirrel", "Prairie dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do all of the U.S. Armed Forces have the rank of General?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sequel to The Lost Boys is titled The Tribe. However, it was originally intended to be entitled The Lost Girls.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This novel written by German author Herman Hesse was published in 1922.", "correct_answer": "Siddhartha", "incorrect_answers": ["Nirvana", "Sartaka", "Samsara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fluffy leader of the G-Force secret agents team?", "correct_answer": "Darwin", "incorrect_answers": ["Mendel", "Cook", "Linnaeus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A virus is a unicellular infectious agent consisting of genetic material encapsulated in a protective protein coat.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This psychiatrist, born in Switzerland in 1875, was one of the founders of analytic psychology.", "correct_answer": "Carl Gustav Jung", "incorrect_answers": ["Johannes Jorenstem", "Erik Jung", "Yokaim Junster"]}]